fivefourclub.com 2016-05-30

# Privacy Policy | Five Four Club | Clothes Delivered To Your Doorstep. New Hand-Picked Gear Every Month.

* * *

### Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. This Privacy Policy addresses how Five Four Group, LLC, parent company of Five Four Club (the “Company”) collects and uses information you provide through your use of and access to the websites located at FiveFourClothing.com or FiveFourClub.com (the “Sites). The Company and the Sites will collectively be referred to referred to herein as “Five Four Club”, "we", "our", or "us”. By visiting, using, accessing the Sites and/or providing your information to us, you agree to accept the practices and terms of this Privacy Policy and also agree to the Terms and Conditions of Five Four. For the rest of this text, Five Four Club is the term that will be used, but it is understood that Five Four Club is a part of Five Four Group, LLC, and thus all rights, obligations, protections, disclaimers, indemnities, and all other legal terms and conditions within this text shall also apply to Five Four Group, LLC.

When you use Five Four Club we gather important information from our users, visitors, subscribers and customers (collectively “user,” “you” or “your”). By visiting, accessing and/or using the Sites and providing your information to us, you acknowledge and agree to this Privacy Policy and also agree to the Terms & Conditions of Five Four Club. We may share information among our subsidiaries or websites that we own or control, but such sharing of information is always governed under the terms of this Privacy Policy. Please further note, depending on your particular interaction with Five Four Club, different portions of this Privacy Policy may apply to your use at different times (e.g. users who solely navigate the website at FiveFourClothing.com or FiveFourClub.com versus users who create an account and purchase the goods and services offered through subscription to the Five Four Club.)

#### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. We group the collection of user information into two categories: Personal and Non-Personal. Personal information is collected upon orders or registering on the Sites and consists of the following: 

  * First and last name;
  * E-mail address;
  * Mailing/billing address;
  * Phone number; or
  * Credit/debit card information

All of the foregoing personal and financial information and related materials shall be collectively referred to hereinafter as “Personal Information”. Any Personal Information you provide to us is voluntary and you can opt out of providing certain Personal Information requested by us. However, your refusal to provide certain Personal Information requested as part of providing Five Four Club may hinder or otherwise restrict your ability to use Five Four Club and its affiliated services. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Non-Personal Information is not identifiable to any specific individual or member and consists of more general demographic information. Non-Personal Information includes, without limitation, the following: age; gender; geographical location based off of IP address; the type of browser and operating system used by users; any interactions users may initiate within Five Four Club; user interactions with the Sites’ features; content preferences users selected within Five Four Club; and other inferences about users’ interests made based upon the foregoing. This information is not intentionally gathered in a fashion to personally identify any single user. We use this information to help us develop Five Four Club, analyze patterns of usage, and make Five Four Club more useful. This information is not used for associating search terms or patterns of site navigation with users.  

#### How do we use your information?

We collect Personal Information to make our services related to this Site ("Services") more rewarding for you to use. Any of the Personal Information we collect from you may be used in the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience and help us to better respond to your individual needs and preferences;
  * To improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you;
  * To improve customer service, allowing us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs;
  * To process transactions, including billing, shipping and tracking your orders;
  * To administer a contest, sweepstakes, giveaway, promotion, survey or other site feature;
  * To send periodic emails for processing and updating you on your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, and related product or service information.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

#### How is this Information Shared?

There are certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Information with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:

  * We may share information about you with trusted third parties to perform functions on our behalf in order to improve your consumer experience. These third parties may contact you about products, services or promotions you may be interested in, or to otherwise improve your customer experience with the Sites. For example, outsourced customer care agents or technology assistants may need access to your information to perform services you requested. Your information will be treated as private and confidential by such service providers and not used for any other purpose than we authorize.
  * In developing and growing our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of corporate sale, merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization or sale of assets, Five Four Club reserves the right to sell or transfer user information (including Personal Information) as part of any such transaction. To the maximum extent allowable by law, the Privacy Policy will apply to the user information as transferred to the successor entity. However, user information submitted after a transfer to a successor entity may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by the successor entity.
  * When it is necessary to protect the rights, property and safety of Five Four Club, its users or the public.
  * As required by law, to comply with a judicial proceeding or court order, to exercise our rights, or to defend against any claims. You acknowledge and agree that we may disclose information you provide if required to do so by law, at the request of a third party, or if we, in our sole discretion, believe that disclosure is reasonable to (1) comply with the law, requests or orders from law enforcement, or any legal process (whether or not such disclosure is required by applicable law); (2) protect or defend Five Four’s, or a third party’s, rights or property; or (3) protect someone’s health or safety, such as when harm or violence against any person (including you) is threatened.

#### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your Personal Information.

All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Stripe software and is accessible only to those authorized with special access rights to such technology and are required to keep the information confidential.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us. Please note that data that is transported over an open network, such as the Internet or e-mail, may be accessible to anybody. We cannot guarantee the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted via such open networks. When disclosing any Personal Information via an open network, you should remain mindful of the fact that it is potentially accessible to others, and consequently, can be collected and used by others without your consent. Your data may be lost during transmission or may be accessed by unauthorized parties. We do not accept any liability for direct or indirect losses as regards the security of your Personal Information or data during its transfer via Internet. Please use other means of communication if you think this is necessary or prudent for security reasons. 

#### Do we use cookies?

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart.

Notice for California Users – Five Four is not presently configured to support Do Not Track (“DNT”) signals from web browsers. 

##### UK Cookies Policy

1\. Definitions  
1.1 In this Cookies Policy the definitions set out in the Terms and Conditions will apply (except where the context otherwise requires)

2\. Five Four’s Cookies  
2.1 We use cookies (small ‘packets’ of data downloaded to your computer, which communicate with our Website and the Website of various third parties) to improve your experience on the Website, to distinguish you from other users and to make your use of the Website as convenient as possible. By using this Website and agreeing to this Cookies Policy, you consent to Five Four Club's use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.  
2.2 There are two types of cookies, session cookies and persistent cookies.  
2.3 Session cookies are persistent cookies files, which are deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies files remain stored until you delete them or until their expiry date.  
2.4 Session cookies are used to remember log in details when you are browsing the Website and to ensure that you are not repeatedly logged out as you browse the Website. The information will be deleted when you close the browser.  
2.5 Persistent cookies store information on your computer so that we will be able to recognise you when you make return visits to the Website, they will be stored on your browser until your erase them or until they expire.  
2.6 The specific Cookies that Five Four will plant on your Computer are as follows:  
AdRoll / Marketing / www.adroll.com  
AppNexus / Advertising / www.appnexus.com  
BidSwitch / Advertising / www.bidswitch.net/  
Customer.io / Marketing / www.customer.io/  
DoubleClick / Advertising / www.google.com/doubleclick/  
Facebook Connect / Marketing / https://developers.facebook.com/  
Facebook Conversion Tracking / Analytics / https://developers.facebook.com/  
Facebook Custom Audience / Marketing / https://developers.facebook.com/  
Facebook Social Plugins / Marketing / https://developers.facebook.com/  
Google Analytics / Analytics / www.google.com/analytics/‎  
Google Dynamic Remarketing / Marketing / https://support.google.com/adwords/answer/3124536?hl=en  
LiveChat / Analytics / http://www.livechatinc.com/  
LiveRamp / Analytics / www.Liveramp.com/  
Mixpanel / Analytics / www.mixpanel.com/‎  
Right Media / Advertising / https://advertising.yahoo.com/Publishers/  
Segment.io / Analytics / https://segment.io/  
Twitter / Advertising / https://ads.twitter.com/

3\. Refusing Cookies  
3.1 Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies in the following way:  
(a) In Internet Explorer, you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector  
(b) In Firefox, you can adjust your cookies setting by clicking “Tools”, “Options” and “Privacy”  
(c) In Google Chrome, you can disable all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Options” and “Under the Bonnet”, then selecting “Content Settings”. 

#### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### Opting Out

We may occasionally send you newsletters and emails regarding special offers, promotions, features and/or product updates. We may also communicate with you on behalf of third parties about special offers, promotions, features and/or product updates we think may be of interest to you, or you may have opted-in to receive newsletters or special promotions from one of our trusted third party providers. If you decide you do not wish to receive these communications, you may opt-out by clicking the unsubscribe link or by following the instructions included in the communication. Note however that as user of the Sites you cannot opt-out of some administrative communications that are reasonably necessary to process your orders, such as billing or service notifications.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your Personal Information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page. 

#### Minors

Five Four Club does not knowingly allow any users under the age of eighteen (18) to use or otherwise access to the Sites or other Five Four Club services. Five Four Club does not wish to collect any Personal Information (or any information at all) from any persons under eighteen (18) years old. If you are under eighteen (18) years old, you may not use Five Four.

#### International Users

Five Four Club is exclusively hosted in the United States. If you are accessing Five Four Club from the European Union, Australia, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, uses, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as such other regions. User information (including Personal Information or “personal data” as defined by foreign laws) collected through Five Four Club may be stored and processed in the United States, and by using Five Four Club, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your home country.

#### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site Privacy Policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Any revised Privacy Policy will apply both to information we already have about you at the time of the change, and any Personal Information created or received after the change takes effect. We strongly recommend that you periodically reread this Privacy Policy, to see if there have been any changes to our policies that may affect you.

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us [online here](https://www.fivefourclub.com/contact), or using the information below.

Five Four Group, LLC   
6213 Randolph Street  
Los Angeles 90040  
USA  

* * *
